

#### HANYANG UNIVERSITY · CHUNGBUK SCIENCE HIGH SCHOOL

Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Rep. of KOREA

□ (+82) 10-3033-5590 | **≤** kyaryunha@naver.com | **⊙** kyaryunha

"I want to be a Great Programmer! Can you help me?"

## **Summary**

I'm a Computer Software freshman.

I learned C language in high school, and it's my first programming language.

I love Problem Solving & Algorithm, so I entered Computer Software.

After the finish university entrance examination, I began to study Web Front End, and It's my first development experience.

When I became a university student, I start studying TeX, 3D Printing, Python, Object Detection(but I don't know ML, just use Tensorflow API).

## **Education**

Hanyang University Seoul, S.Korea

COMPUTER SOFTWARE Mar. 2019

• 222, Wangsimni-ro, Seongdong-gu, Seoul, 04763, Korea

## Skills

**Programming Language** C, C++, TeX, Python, JavaScript

Web Front-End HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

**3D Printing** Fusion 360

**Illustration** Clip Studio, Photoshop

**Development Tools** Github, CodeBlocks, VS Code, Atom, Pycharm, TeX Studio, Overleaf

**Try a little** Kotlin, Aheui(아호), Jetson Nano, Object Detection

**Others** Data Structure, Algorithm

#### Awards

### **ALGORITHM**

| 2016 | Encouragement Prize(167th), KOI(Korean Olympiad in Informatics)            | KIISE            |
|------|--|------------------|
| 2016 | Excellence Prize Prize(6th), National High School Girl Programming Contest | Ewha Womans Univ |
| 2017 | Silver Prize(29th), KOI(Korean Olympiad in Informatics)                    | KIISE            |
| 2017 | Finalist, NEXON Youth Programming Challenge                                | NEXON            |
| 2018 | Asia 308th, Kor 23rd, Asia Pacific Information Olympiad                    | Innopolis        |
| 2018 | Finalist, NEXON Youth Programming Challenge                                | NEXON            |
| 2019 | 27th, UCPC(National College Student Programming Contest)                   | UCPC             |
| 2019 | 23place(50th), ICPC Seoul Regional   | ICPC             |

#### **Presentation**

#### T<sub>E</sub>X Book Design: Page styles and Title

Kongju, S.Korea

Nov. 2019

THE KOREAN TEX SOCIETY WORKSHOP

• Introduce about how design pagestyles using TFX's package memoir

- Translation and summary about Madsen's pagestyles manual.
- Introduce about my document design using memoir
- http://wiki.ktug.org/wiki/wiki.php/LaTeXWorkshop/2019

DECEMBER 13, 2019 SHIN HYUN · CV 1

# **Work Experience**

#### Try to Solve 4x4x4 Magic Cube Using Simulated Annealing

Cheongju, S.Kored

2018 CHUNGBUK SCIENCE HIGH SCHOOL MATH MAGAZINE

Mar.2018 - Apr. 2018

- Magic Cube is a number from 1 to 64 arranged in a cube-like arrangement so that the sum of 76 horizontal, vertical, and diagonal segments is equal.
- Way to arrange 64 in a cube with about  $10^{18}$
- · Finding an array that satisfies about 38 segments in about 9 seconds using the Simulated Annealing technique

My Site Cheongju, S.Korec

FIRST WEB FRONT END WORK

Sep. 2018 - Oct. 2018

- · HTML, CSS, Javascript
- 1. Sleep Computer(Fill the screen with the desired color)
- 2. Arithmetic Sequence Game(Play 7\*7 Arithmetic Sequence game, This game made by me.)
- kyaryunha.com

**Draw Graph**Cheongju, S.Korec

SECOND WEB FRONT END WORK

Nov. 2018

- Click for draw the vertices and edges of the graph
- · HTML, CSS, Javascript
- · Custom vertices and edges of different shapes, colors, and sizes
- · kyaryunha.com/drawgraph

Christmas Tree Cheongiu, S.Kored

THIRD WEB FRONT END WORK

Dec. 2018

- Draw Christmas Tree (Forest)
- · HTML, CSS, Javascript
- · Edges directly connected to the root are colored brown, and edges not associated with the root are colored green
- Restricts drawing of non-tree(forest) graphs
- When MST mode is activated, Minimum Spanning Tree is automatically calculated
- kyaryunha.com/christmas

3D Printing Seoul, S.Korea

HANYANG UNIV ENGINEERING ACADEMIC CLUB BARAMI, HANYANG ACADEMIC TOWN PROGRAM

Mar. 2019 - Apr. 2019

- · Studying 3D Modeling, Simulation, and Rapid Prototyping Using Fusion 360 and Assembling 3D Printer Prusa MK3
- Producing by modeling some necessary parts in the club

Catch Catch Seoul, S.Korea

SOFTWARE MAESTRO 10TH, TEAM.CATCH CATCH

Jun. 2019 - Nov. 2019

- Digital media interactive content for pets
   Real Time Object Detection Cat and Dog using Haar Cas
- · Real Time Object Detection Cat and Dog using Haar Cascade, Mask RCNN, YOLO(Darknet), mobilenetSSD(Caffe, Tensorflow) on Windows
- Collect Image Data about Cat Top View
- Labeling and Training Cat, Cat's head, Cat's paw at mobilenetSSD(Tensorflow)
- · Real Time Object Detection Cat, Cat's head, Cat's paw using mobilenetSSD(Tensorflow) on Windows
- Real Time Object Detection Cat and Dog using mobilenetSSD(TensorRT), Yolo(Darknet, TensorRT), Tiny Yolo(Darknet) on Jetson Nano
- Printing product case made with Fusion360

# **School Activity**

### Hanyang Univ Engineering Academic Club BARAMI

Seoul, S.Korea Mar. 2019 - PRESENT

MEMBER (MAR. 2019), VICE-PRESIDENT (DEC. 2019)

- Electrical and Bio-Engineering, Electronic Engineering, Computer Software's club
- Hold and take long-term and short-term seminars
- · Exhibition of works in November every year
- Dec. 2019, Be elected Vice-President

DECEMBER 13, 2019 SHIN HYUN · CV